Don't know how many times
I've been crossed off the
list and left for dead.
Guess when it first happens
the day you were born...
you're gonna lose count.
So this...
this ain't nothing new.
There are bad days...
and then there are
legendary bad days.
This was shaping up
to be one of those.
Whole damn planet
wanted a piece of me.
Can't stay in the open.
Can't risk another attack.
It's always the punch you don't
see coming that puts you down.
But why didn't I see it?
Of course they were
gonna try to kill me.
Death is what they
do for a living.
So the question ain't
"What happened?"
The question is...
"What happened to me?"
You are the Lord Marshal now.
How did they get so close?
How did I let them
blindside me like that?
Threshold! Take us
to the threshold!
Necromongers.
Some wanted to put a
crown on my head.
noose around my neck.
Please...
come back to bed.
Every Lord Marshal was supposed
to take some big oath...
one that I never
really got around to.
You could say it created
a little friction...
and more than a few assassins.
I needed a way out.
Some new place.
Or maybe just...
an old one.
Furya.
I know what it's called.
You just don't know where it is.
- I need charts. I need maps.
- Impossible.
I need a direction.
Purged from all records,
as you well know.
But you remember where,
Commander Vaako.
So many worlds...
The only map left
in existence...
is the one that's in my head...
Riddick.
So what do you want?
The crown?
Transcendence.
Krone.
Break off a ship.
Riddick's going home.
Vaako.
You can't blame him
for dangling Furya.
Home has a certain equity.
But I do blame him
for what came next.
It's a long way to come.
For this.
This guy with the
fucked-up face, Krone...
he was supposed to
be our ride home.
But instead of Furya, we
wind up someplace called...
Not Furya.
Yet again, someone was
trying to play me.
So yet again...
we play for blood.
You keep what you kill, Riddick!
You keep what you kill!
Somewhere along the
way, I lost a step.
I got sloppy.
Dulled my own edge.
Maybe I went and did the
worst crime of all...
I got civilized.
So now we zero the clock.
Just me and this no-name world.
Gotta find that
animal side again.
Before long...
I realized there was a whole
other world over there...
of water, grass and life.
Just had one thing in my way.
Come on, show me some teeth.
Escape artist, huh?
What have you got over there?
Thought we shared everything.
Drop it.
Stay.
Bounty hunters...
Wait.
Wait...
Steady...
Okay, now.
Sounds good.
All yours.
It says "dog food" on it.
If you could read.
Come on...
Alright. Bring me my reserve.
Where's yours?
Rain.
It's a good thing.
Just because you've never seen it
before doesn't mean it's a bad thing.
Hey... easy...
Looks like our time is up here.
Nothing.
Look again, Diaz.
Somebody should teach this
Riddick asshole how to count.
"Leave one ship"?
Like we've got a fucking
spare laying around.
Let's crank it up.
Morning, Cyclops.
Hey, Luna.
Yeah.
Wake her up, kick her outta bed.
What do you mean?
We're running heavy.
She's a prisoner.
- Wasn't she gonna pay our way back?
- We're going big now.
Okay? Cut that 60 kilos loose.
- Get away! Get away from me!
- Stop, just stop!
What do you want now?
I'm gonna take off the restraints.
Okay?
- I don't want them off.
- No, it's not like that.
Nobody's gonna touch you now.
Santana's head is
into other stuff now.
Your lucky day.
- Get the fuck away from me.
- Alright.
What planet is this?
Where are we?
It's got air and water.
That's all you gotta know.
- But how am I supposed to survive?
- Just go.
Before he changes his mind.
I was getting attached to her.
Now where is my box at?
The name...
is Santana!
Shot-caller for this
crew right here!
I am the guy who knows
all, sees all, beats all!
Spitting it kinda
strong, ain't he?
Gotta bait the trap.
I've come all this way to
collect your head in a box!
Right here!
So have yourself a
fine day now...
Mr. Richard B. Riddick!
I suspect...
it will be one...
of your very last!
Well, you don't need to agitate
Riddick any more than... you know.
Any more than bringing his
head back in a box would?
Shit.
Here comes the neighborhood.
Small world.
Unidentified vessel, this is
Clan Vagos out of Ursa Five.
Be advised that we are
on the ground now
and have responded
to emergency signal.
No distress found,
no need to land.
I repeat, there is no reason for you
to land at this location at this time.
Is that clear?
No reason for you to land at
this location at this time.
What the fuck did I just say?!
It was a long haul. We
could take on some water.
Wouldn't mind a little
true-gravity time either.
Like I was saying,
I've got this.
You know who that was, right?
On the emergency beacon?
Wouldn't be here if I didn't.
The concept of back-up still
has no appeal to you?
My besties here can
ball with anyone.
No disrespect for
your crew, of course,
who look strong, too, in
those matchy-matchyoutfits.
Shit. Didn't know there
was a dress code.
Yeah, right?
Well, it's not my intention
to jump another man's claim.
If you don't mind, maybe we'll just pull
up a chair and spectate for a while.
What if I do?
This is a Co-op station, pal.
It's open to all mercs.
- By the way, my name is...
- "Too late".
That's your name. Too Late.
And I don't need you stepping all
over my dick here, my friend.
Well, I tell you what.
I won't lift a finger to help you until
you come ask me for it. How's that?
I was scoping this out earlier. It's
a cave system . Five clicks South.
Might be worth a look.
Hey, Too Late.
Need to pull a node from your ship and
store it right here next to mine. Okay?
Oh, really? Why's that?
Riddick triggered the beacon
to get off-world, right?
Basically, he was
calling a taxi.
And ...?
And a ship would make
a sweet trap, right?
Confined space, metal walls...
jail cell.
Ace cool, huh?
Is it true half the people you meet
are below average intelligence?
Got to make sure the ship stays
grounded when he comes for them, okay?
Come on.
Dahl... pull a node
from the ship.
I'll do it!
Any time now, Riddick.
I'm telling you, this is total overkill.
Eleven of us out here now?
Should have been a
four-man op, tops.
You are jinxing our janx, man.
And that ain't cool.
Hey, I don't give a shit what they say.
He's one guy.
Whatever you say.
So I guess that's what passes for
a fucking moon on this planet.
It's gonna be a dark night.
Advantage, him.
Maybe he's gonna wear you down first.
Force you to go without sleep.
Can't you see I'm busy?
I'm just sharing my thoughts.
Well, now that you have...
can I politely invite you to
step off my fucking porch?!
I'll start rotating down.
You let me know, huh?
As soon as I have his head in
a box, I will let you know.
Grid 2gD. Stand by, stand by.
What you got, cuz?
Some dingo-dongo thing.
Yeah . I see it now.
You want me to pop it?
Knock it down. One
shot suppressed.
Nice work, Diaz. Encouraging.
Had something in my eye.
It's called a scope.
Try next time.
You got this, right?
Will you get off my
freaking frequency!
What the fuck is going on here?
Thank fucking God!
Fuck off!
Rubio, coming your way now.
Gotta swap out a bad sensor.
What was here versus
what was found.
How does it square?
Pretty good . The morphine's gone, but
that's always the first thing to go.
That was a bit weird, though.
"A predator restraint with
42-inch offset jaws."
Six listed, zero found.
Well, it is an odd thing
to go for a walk.
Yeah, but Boss, you know how shit
goes missing from these stations.
One bad year and guys are
ripping shit off for salvage.
Hey, Santana?
You did sweep the area
before I got here, right?
Sweep for what?
Well, I just want to make sure
no one has set any traps for us.
5Q.
- Understand what I'm saying?
- Traps?
What kind of traps?
The kind with jaws.
Don't touch that fucking thing!
What?
Up-armor.
Shit!
Ready, ready.
Stay put, stay put!
Who the hell was that
screaming and why?
Nunez...
break out the sweep gear.
And figure out how many
of these big-ass traps...
we got out here, okay?
I'm thinking maybe the whole upper left
quad is some kind of fucking mine field.
You do that now, okay, Nunez?
Copy that, Nunez?
Nunez?
This is bad. This is very bad.
- Nunez? Nunez?
- Shut the fuck up, puto!
His radio just crapped out.
Someone get eyes on him.
- And show him right where he should be.
- 13H. Go, 90, 90!
Right here.
13-H . He's supposed
to be right fucking...
So this was overkill, huh?
Eleven of us, too many, yeah.
You know all about
Riddick, right?
Well, maybe you need to
take that shit back!
Take the jinx off our janx.
You understand me?
That's what you need to do, Falco. You
need to unjinxelate our fucking janx!
Don't mess with me now.
Hey, what is it?
- Get back!
- It's me, it's me.
He's got Falco!
Jock up, but you're
staying home.
No one's going out
there until I say so.
- Man down, he got Falco.
- Compromise, compromise.
- How the fuck did he do that?
- Never even saw him. He was right here...
What about the ship?
Is he on it?
He's not coming for the ships, he's coming for us!
Just fucking shoot!
One night, three dead.
Not sure I'm loving this trend.
Two dead, one missing.
Exactly. Three dead.
Well, look at it this way, boys.
We might all fit
on one ship now.
Diaz!
Get those other
traps back there.
Luna, say something
Bible-like over these bodies.
Okay, maybe...
we zero this out.
What is your tag anyway?
So now you wanna know my name.
Well, I'm not sure
I'm gonna say.
Because everyone you know by
name, Santana, winds up dead.
You gonna clean this shit up?
Shut up, fucking bitch!
Excuse me.
Watch out for surprise attacks.
Maybe...
Maybe it's time to start
merging assets, right?
So this is you
asking for my help?
This is me saying that I may
need some of your gear.
If some of your guys happen to
come attached to that gear...
I will understand that's
the way it's gotta be.
So you're asking for
my gear's help?
More like that.
Moss...?
The gear says "nah". Bitch.
There's your answer.
What the fuck do you want, man?
You know what? I'm gonna
fold you in, Santana.
But I give orders to Dahl. And
Dahl's gonna give orders to you.
And that's the chain of command
from this point forward.
Why am I not loving
this plan so far?
Oh, I know. You know why?
Because it sucks
ass and swallows!
I'm not taking orders from your pet whore
who thinks I won't smack her right back...
I don't fuck guys.
Occasionally I fuck'em
up if they need it.
Here's what's gonna happen, Santana.
You're gonna take a back seat.
We'll track Riddick
down, I promise.
But I want him alive.
You give me a day and after
that he's yours to kill.
You're giving me the bounty?
You pay my crew, fuel costs, the rest is yours.
That's the deal.
What is Riddick for you?
Not just some convict.
What do you want?
Why are you here?
Who are you?
My name is Johns.
Lock down those ships,
get those hogs on deck.
I will ride with
Moss and Lockspur.
I want a non-lethal load-out. L.O.D.'s
and phosphor frags to start with.
This is a man that hunts by night.
We'll take it to him by day.
Diaz! Vargas! Show me the
spot of the last kill.
Some kind of canine.
Hey, Diaz, I've got a dog here.
Is it the same dingo-dongo
thing from last night?
Nah, I'm pretty sure
we killed that one.
Could be the same one.
The same.
Dahl, get your sniper rifle
and barium rounds now.
1500 meters.
Could be just the
first hole it found.
A stressed animal is gonna
run to ground it knows.
Besides... I'm getting
human pheromones.
Riddick!
Dial down, dial down, dial down!
- Santana's guy.
- Falco.
Shit. Did we just
kill a hostage?
I've been hunting
Riddick for ten years.
The concept of a hostage
has no appeal to him.
Falco was already dead.
This is just some fucking
side-show to buy more time.
Fuck!
Shit...
Just dropped some
mud right there.
So if Riddick isn't here...
Dahl, do you copy?
Does anyone copy?
Dahl, you there?
Boom.
Were you just perving
out on me somehow?
May all your dreams
come true, baby.
You've got two minutes. I want
you out on fucking watch.
Luna!
Don't watch me. Watch my back.
That's what you're here for.
Take two steps forward . Two.
Remember, he could be anywhere.
This is Johns to
any-goddamn-body at the station.
I want you to keep an ey e on that locker.
Keep an ey e on the node.
Riddick may have
made an end run.
My ETA is seven minutes.
But watch your back.
Where did you go, bitch?
Your two minutes are up. You
gonna do what I tell you to do?
Rumor is Riddick might
be in the vicinity.
Thought I should just
check on the locker.
Get outside, get on your optics,
and get after this fucker!
You're not gonna find him here.
Actually, Dahl, I think we
have something in common.
I don't fuck guys either.
You need to see this.
He wrote that?
He took out our deep space
communications. All of it.
And whose blood is that?
There...? Here...?
Over there...?
I had to kick his ass again.
Sorry.
Not really.
Fuck it.
Let's take a look at this.
Stop.
That key leave your neck?
Never.
Well, the only reason to
write "fair trade"...
is if he got into that locker
and he took something out.
Something that we need,
like a power node...
which he could then swap
for something he needs.
All that? Wow.
Highly unlikely.
Let me connect the
fucking dots, Santana.
Here's what I'm saying. If
he did get in there somehow,
he was in a position to relock
it and change the code.
Could be entering the
wrong shit, Santana.
So...
do you think sometime during
the last few hours...
he got this off my neck
without me noticing...
did whatever he did, put
the fucking key back
on my fucking neck without
me fucking noticing?
Is that what you're saying?
Where did you get that theory from?
A unicorn's ass?
There's a reason
he is who he is.
He's a convict. Not
some Zulu warlock.
You know what you know.
This is crazy.
This is fucking crazy. The
first three clicks were good.
It did not go off.
You can get three clicks
in Russian Roulette.
Don't mean you get
four, motherfucker.
You know what, Santana? For
once I actually agree with you.
Shut up.
You... Do you think we're good?
Yeah.
I think you're good, cuz.
You're fucking good.
Just butch up.
Sounds like your
department, lesbo.
I'm not opening that thing.
- Oh yes, you fucking are!
- I'm so fucking not!
Hey, hey! Use your
fucking brains!
We are not gonna do
Riddick's work for him!
Put your weapons down.
And have a look at that.
He was here.
Right fucking there.
Santana, put your
fucking sword away.
Don't fucking open it, then.
Well, the problem with that, Santana,
we never open that locker...
and we never leave.
...of my life and my
salvation Whom shall I fear.
The strength of my life of
Whom shall I be afraid.
Four.
Try five.
Five.
And...
Oops.
Wish I'd have thought of that.
Six!
Six.
You are a shit storm trooper, Santana.
I'll give you that.
You beat the devil this time.
Didn't actually think
he was gonna do it.
This is a sign.
Sweet.
I believe this is a sign.
It may be the good Lord wants
us to take these nodes...
and flee this planet
just as soon as we can.
That's my good luck charm.
Wrong business, kid.
You know, I was kind of
hoping the bomb would go off.
So we sealed up his cave with some
phosphor frags here, so he can't go back.
And just like an animal, he's
gonna head to known ground.
But we're gonna find he's got
three or four layers out there.
So we'll radius out from
this point... here.
That radio counts. I saw three
repeaters listed in inventory.
Find them. Set them up
at regular intervals.
I never want to be out of
communication like that again.
Are you scared of me?
Yeah.
Are they scared of me?
Yes, they're scared of you.
Maybe you're all scared
of the wrong thing.
Lockspur, I want you to lock
down those hogs, alright?
I don't want this guy any more
mobile than he already is.
Dahl, I spotted a nice
little nest for you.
Right here and in
these low hills.
Moss?
I just saw him.
Say it again?
Dahl, I want you to
sit on this ship!
Diaz, make sure your
ship is locked down!
The rest of you get on the fucking perimeter
and keep your eyes on each other!
Santana! He got the
fucking nodes!
I know. It's coming.
So then we just combine nodes.
Pull one from that ship, put
it in this ship, you know?
Amps is amps, right?
It's not about amps. It's about
what each ship is rated to handle.
You miss by even a few milli-joules,
you fry every chip you've got.
Okay, so figure out the
difference, and just do it.
Jailbreak the fucking thing.
I could give you a crash course
on thermodynamic equilibrium and
energy exchange right now...
or maybe you just want to
take my goddamn word for it.
I get it, I get it.
The ships are incompatible. We're not
gonna fly without the nodes back.
Why do I feel like we just
cut off our own nuts here?
Probably because we did.
How about I take one of those jet
hogs, two days worth of food...
and go out and hunt this
fucker down myself.
Bad idea, Diaz.
One-on-one with Riddick?
I might be able to get the
emergency beacon working again.
That's like an ambulance calling
for an ambulance, isn't it?
It's back-up for the fucking back-up.
We can't.
I thought he was the
one stranded here.
Yeah, well, looks like
you thought wrong.
Long wait for back-up.
In case you were thinking about fixing
the beacon and calling for help.
Falco's radio.
Riddick, I don't give a
fuck about the back-up.
Because I've still got all kinds of
gear that can ruin your day in a hurry.
So you go find another
fucking cave.
You keep running,
you keep hiding.
Doesn't matter to me.
Because in the end,
I will find you!
Look South.
I don't believe it.
The balls on this fucking guy.
Dahl, keep an eye
on things here.
- What should I do?
- Stay low.
Come on . Come on.
Both of you drop.
So what's the bounty at?
I don't know. I don't care.
It's not why I'm here.
I bet the big jamoke knows.
Yeah . I know
exactly what it is.
What I do know is that it's double
if you're brought back dead.
That's new.
Will it be enough to
pay for your funerals?
What I'm interested in...
is a little backwater place
with a system code M-344-G.
I want to know what happened
there ten years ago.
The father.
- Big Daddy Johns.
- Yeah, that's right.
And you traveled all
this way just to see me.
I'm flattered.
Well, it's kind of strange not knowing
what to put down in the family Bible.
It's kinda strange three guys have
to die just to you can hear...
No, no, no. You don't get
to put that shit on me.
Those kills are on you.
I have a feeling that's not the
only thing on me right now.
Okay, got barium shells,
stab-shock, explosive tip...
What do you want,
barium or stab-shock?
Horse tranq.
I hate to interrupt this
discussion about ancient history,
but maybe I should step in right
here and introduce myself.
- My name is...
- Box Boy.
Say what?
You are the guy who said that he was
gonna put my head in a box. Right?
Well, that was me...
spitting noise.
But you do have a box.
Do I have a box?
Thought I saw one.
I mean, of course I've got a box.
Everyone's got a box, man.
Even Diaz has a
fucking huge box.
Good.
We're gonna use it.
Three down, eight left.
Now, normally I'd
just keep going.
Six down... nine down...
You get where I'm
going with this.
But things are changing here...
and nobody wants to be on this
planet 24 hours from now.
So I suggest we make it work.
What do you want, a
"gentleman's agreement"?
I'll leave one node out in the open.
You take it.
The other node and the
other ship are mine.
Hey, wait, wait.
What are we playing here,
Retard Bingo? What?
- That was on the table from the start...
- Forget the start.
It's the end you want
to think about now.
See that?
I'll give you till that
rain hits that station.
That's your clock.
"Box Boy".
Dahl! Do it now! Now!
Again!
He's not going down.
Do it again, Dahl!
Just go down.
I got this, Dahl.
Riddick.
Riddick?
Johns?
You beating men in chains now?
Okay, from the beginning. For
the historical record...
The Hunter Gratzner.
That's the commercial vessel my son uses
to transport you back to the slammer.
But that ship sends a distress
call somewhere near M-344 /G.
It's a backwater system, two
suns, one habitable planet.
Does he survive the crash?
Big drama the next few hours.
But whatever happens, no
matter what they tell you...
don't let 'em take
these chains off me.
"Them?" Who's "them?" Who're you talking...
Do you know who you're talking to here?
That was for me?
When the chains come off...
- Jesus Christ!
- Box Boy...
you go in the first
five seconds.
Really?
And you plan on killing
me with what, your mouth?
That shiny blade.
I'd love to see you try.
For the historical record...
he made it.
So it's just you and him?
Was, uh...
about the same number you
see here in this room.
So now many made it off?
Three.
But not him?
No.
So between the time of the crash and
the time you leave that planet...
my son dies.
And I can safely assume it's at your hands.
Is that right?
I'm wasting my
fucking time here!
You grant any last wishes?
I was referring to you.
Not that the chains aren't
a hot look, but no.
I'm not gonna straddle you
in front of all these guys.
What if I killed
all of 'em first?
Easy, boy.
There's a lot more tranq
where that came from.
Tell me what you see
outside that window, Dahl.
Cyclops unit, two ships...
couple dead guys in plastic.
And you don't see anything else?
Nothing else.
Let me know when you do.
Love those toenails, by the way.
Yeah?
Predator Pink.
Matches your nipples.
Why are we even listening
to this big fuckstick?
Can we just detach
his head, please?
Here's what's gonna happen.
The next 60 seconds, you're gonna watch
your own head drop into that box.
Nothing...
nothing is gonna keep you from
that special place in Hell.
Maybe in the last minute of your life,
you want to be something more...
than a goddamn savage!
Gimme some fucking answers!
Please!
Well, is there anything you'd like
to add on the subject I just raised?
Time's up.
He's all yours.
Hold him down.
End of game, dude.
More dingo-dongos maybe.
Fuck it.
I know what's coming.
Called to find you.
The serpents...
Spotlight!
Like I said...
it ain't me you
gotta worry about.
What is it? What's out there?
I don't know.
Fucked up or
something out there.
It ain't right. It's
coming our way.
Whatever they are, they
ain't so hard to kill.
What the fuck?!
Fuck!
No more holes, please.
Now here's what's gonna happen.
In 60 seconds you're gonna
take these chains off me.
We're gonna make a play for those
nodes and get off this rock.
But somewhere along the line...
when it gets really bad...
Johns...
is gonna fold just
like Little Johns did.
Then when it's all over...
and the rest of you are ready
for Dead Animal Pickup...
I'm gonna go balls
deep into Dahl.
But only because
she asked me to.
Sweet-like.
What does he mean, "When things go bad"?
This doesn't qualify as bad?!
What the fuck is happening?
How fucked are we?
Who knows how long it will rain?
Or just how many of them
are buried out there?
He saw it. He saw it with those eyes
of his and he didn't tell us what.
One ship for you, one for me.
I need to know that these
nodes are retrievable.
And I need to know
we have a deal.
We got a deal.
The chains stay on.
Why don't we sit this one out?
Okay, okay.
Up, up, up, up,
up, up, up, up...
Good doggie.
Holy... shit.
Yeah.
Let's cut him loose.
That was five seconds.
I like to be a man of my word.
How about you, Johns?
He shall give His angels charge over
me, keep me in all His grace...
- Shut the noise, Luna!
- As long as I live.
You know, I think the angels
are here protecting me.
And if they're here,
watching over me...
Maybe they'll deliver us...
- all from this crazy-shit place.
- That shit is creeping everybody out...
- so shut the fuck up!
- You shut the fuck up, Vargas!
Leave the kid alone.
Where the hell did that...?
Jesus Christ!
No, no, no, no!
What the fuck is wrong with
you, you crazy bastard!
You could have killed me!
Got it, didn't I?
Vargas, get up.
Come on, let's go!
Vargas, come on, man . Walk it off.
Let's go. It's just a little one.
Small ones are the worst.
They save the most venom.
And kid?
Leave God out of this.
He wants no part of
what happens next.
I forgot to mention...
there's no weapons for you.
You think you can ride
one of these things?
I'll ride it like I stole it.
I'll take flank.
If Riddick comes back
here without us...
you go ahead, you kill him
on General principle.
Is that before or after
I'm supposed to fuck him?
You asshole motherfucker!
Just sitting there watching!
Would have covered you, but
you said "no weapons".
I bet you want those
nodes, Johns.
Hey, I don't suppose you took the
time to do this for him, huh?
This may come as a
shock to you, Johns...
but I didn't ghost your son.
He seemed set on
killing himself.
What the fuck does that mean?
Morphine.
Your son liked his morphine.
Liked it twice a day.
Didn't know your
son was a junkie?
Johns was like most mercs.
They look all stand-up
and do-right...
until you cut them open and
you find something missing.
In his case, a spine.
I don't have to listen to this shit!
That's not the man I knew.
Then you didn't know your son.
He wanted to kill a kid.
To save his own skin.
I had a problem with that.
You expect me to believe...
my son was gonna kill a
child to save his own life?
Morphine makes the brain soft.
Heart wrong.
I don't fucking buy it!
I just can't believe that
my son's the bad guy
in this fucking demented
fairy tale of yours.
No reason to lie now...
Johns.
Either one of us.
Thanks for starting the killing
spree for me, Riddick.
But I'll take it from here.
Jamoke.
So that blade you buried
was meant for me?
Anyone who deserved it, really.
We've got a problem, Riddick...
because I've got two nodes here.
We've got one hog.
And I sure as shit am not
riding bitch with you again.
One hog?
You sure about that, Johns?
He pulled the goddamn
turbine pin!
You just figured that out?
Diaz was gonna take the nodes
for himself and ghost me.
He was gonna leave
you out here alone.
So what now?
Now we switch to
our ground game.
Let's see if that lack of
spine runs in the family.
Reload!
Watch your head.
Go!
I got inbound.
Take this!
Is it just you?
Just slam this thing in.
See if it's still good.
Boss...
Just see if the fucking thing works!
We need to get outta here.
Extraction, 30 seconds or less.
Let's go, let's go!
Let me ask you something...
sweet-like...
Lot of good men
died here, Riddick.
Not sure how I'm supposed to
overlook that. Next time.
Yeah . Things would
have been different
if they weren't trying
to put my head in a box.
So where to now, Riddick?
You know what? Fuck that. Don't tell me.
I don't wanna know.
I'll tell you this, Johns.
Sooner or later, we all
have to head home.
Tell Dahl to keep
it warm for me.
And Johns...
you keep a strong spine.